[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these terms refers to the formation of blood cells?", "correct_answer": "Haematopoiesis", "incorrect_answers": ["Haematogenesis", "All of these", "Haematophagus"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Very Large Array (VLA) is a radio astronomy observatory located on the Plains of San Augustin, USA, consisting of what number of separate radio antennae?", "correct_answer": "27", "incorrect_answers": ["35", "12", "19"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie 8 Mile, B-Rabbit knew his moms boyfriend before she started going out with him? Where had he met the guy?", "correct_answer": "B-Rabbit went to school with him.", "incorrect_answers": ["He is B-Rabbits father and his moms ex-husband.", "He is in the group of people that B-Rabbit hangs out with.", "B-Rabbit met him at a rap off."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the length of an average Stegosaurus?", "correct_answer": "26-30 feet (8-9.2 m)", "incorrect_answers": ["20-28 feet (6-8.5 m)", "30-40 feet (9.2-12.2 m)", "34-38 feet (10.4-11.5 m)"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What movie of the Honey, I Shrunk the Kids series was released in 1989?", "correct_answer": "Honey, I Shrunk the Kids", "incorrect_answers": ["Honey, We Shrunk Ourselves", "None of these", "Honey, I Blew Up the Kid"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The worlds largest brewer is based in:", "correct_answer": "Belgium", "incorrect_answers": ["Germany", "The Netherlands", "The USA"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In Its a Mad, Mad, Mad, Mad World, what happens at the new gas station owned by Irwin and Ray?", "correct_answer": "Lennie Pike destroys the gas station.", "incorrect_answers": ["All of the various groups looking for the money show up at the gas station at the same time.", "nothing", "The gas station blows up."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In 1945, Robert Altman joined the military service and served as what?", "correct_answer": "a pilot", "incorrect_answers": ["a marine", "a sapper", "a member of tank crew"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who was the first Major League Baseball player born in what was then called Czechoslovakia?", "correct_answer": "Elmer Valo", "incorrect_answers": ["Reno Bertoia", "Ernie Orvitz", "Andy Pafko"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What star is closest to the sun?", "correct_answer": "Proxima Centauri", "incorrect_answers": ["Procima Beta", "Alpha Centauri", "Proxima Alpha"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Ernest Borgnine played General Worden in this 1967 hit military movie.", "correct_answer": "The Dirty Dozen", "incorrect_answers": ["The Wild Bunch", "The Dirty Dozen II", "Bad Day At Black Rock"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What type of food is rich in tryptophan, and therefore prevents and cures depression?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Nuts", "Dairy", "Meat"]}]